<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Epidemiology | Adrian Zucco</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tag/epidemiology/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tag/epidemiology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Epidemiology</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/icon_hu6038dbd17db210a07028cde60a2399e9_12361_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Epidemiology</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tag/epidemiology/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>DANLIFE (The DANish LIFE course cohort)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/danlife/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/danlife/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The DANish LIFE course cohort (DANLIFE) is a nationwide, register-based, life-course cohort that is based on comprehensive and continuously updated information on social adversity and major life events from the Danish registers. These unique data from a large, unselected population provide an unprecedented resource for testing life-course mechanisms, such as sensitive periods and the accumulation of various stress factors across childhood, adolescence and young adulthood.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disease trajectories in the European Health Data Space (EHDS)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/ehds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/ehds/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall goal of this use case is to study longitudinal health trajectories - and in particular those leading to cardiometabolic diseases. Furthermore it will assess how these trajectories compare across nationwide registries from France, Norway, Finland and Denmark. This project seeks to define health trajectories as the longitudinal sequence of health-related events (e.g. disease diagnoses, medications and hospitalizations) that precede a main outcome of interest, for example, a myocardial infarction.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Young Sleep Program</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/young_sleep/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/young_sleep/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
